

John Clark Smart Contract Developer

About Me

- 7 years of smart contract experience

From Launching token to DEFI, I have deep experience in the blockchain industry with professional skills about designing, developing, and auditing smart contracts.

Have succeeded in delivering tokens, and make social events with it on several companies. Now researching cutting-edge technology on blockchain using Golang and Rust to implement L2 Networks.

Professional Skills

Blockchain	Solidity
Web3	Ethers
Hardhat	Truffle

Work Experience

Smart Contract Developer at Foxbit

Oct 2020 - Present

Foxibit is a safe and advanced cryptocurrency trading platform and utility tokens, stable coins and tokenized real assets.

- Build Smart Contract for MasterChef Staking Platform to provide rewards for holders.
- Build Smart Contract for Swap Router & Factory to implement DEX and Yield Farming with collaborating with other DEFIs.
- Make test scripts for existing smart contracts and gas optimization with gas reporter.

Skills: Solidity, DEFI, Web3, Hardhat

Smart Contract Developer at Bunzz

Nov 2016 - Sep 2020

Bunzz is a Smart Ecosystem for Smart Contracts on All kinds of Blockchain Industry.

- Research Smart Contracts with Open-Source Libraries on Popular Ecosystems.
- Build Smart Contracts for ERC20, NFT, DEFI and DAO systems.
- Audit Smart Contract and build Documents for newly added contract on the Platforms.
- Supporting Projects for using the Platforms and customize Smart Contract for Clients.

Skills: Solidity, CrossChain, Ethers, Audit

Education

Bachelor of Science (with Honors) Degree in Computing from University of London

2013 - 2016